<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Camping</string>
    <string name="kabak_cove_info">Kabak Cove, which has been popular especially among young people in recent years, is impressed by its high hills and deep blue sea. There are various camping areas in the region. Of course, camping everywhere is forbidden. You can also stay in bungalows if you wish. In order to get to the bay, which is a bit difficult to reach, you have to take the Faralya minibuses from the center of Fethiye. After getting off at the last stop, you have to walk for half an hour and take a tractor or taxi. In Kabak Valley, located on the bay, guests with a tent can rent the camping area for 100 TL per day. Canopy, music and food are also offered by the facility. Guests without tents can stay in tents for 2 or 3 people for 125 TL per person.</string>
    <string name="macka_info">Trabzon Livera Camping, located in Maçka, is another place where you can camp if you want to enjoy the green ... The business generates its energies from the sun and wind in order to continue eco tourism. With its unique vegetation, wildlife, crater lake, steep hillside valleys and lined mountains, it keeps campers away from noisy and stressful environments and brings them together with nature. If you have a tent in the facility, the area rental fee is 30 TL. When you go to the camping area, which is about 8-9 km from the center of Maçka, be sure to visit the Sumela Monastery.</string>
    <string name="salda_lake_info">Turkeys Maldives titles Salt Lake which is quite popular in recent years, are in demand by campers. No fee is charged for those who want to set up their own tents. Enchanting with its white sand and turquoise water, the lake was formed by a volcanic eruption. It has a very special similarity with Mars. White sediments on the shore of the lake are also present exactly on Mars. A place to be protected, where not a single matchstick should be thrown away. If you camp here, you can also use toilets, showers and changing cabins.</string>
    <string name="camlihemsin_info">There are so many places to camp in Çamlıhemşin, the natural wonder of Rize ... Whichever one you prefer, you can feel the sound of the creek flowing next to you and the smell of pine forests. Of course, lets warn in advance… The weather in the plateaus changes very quickly. You have a chance to not see the view because of the sudden fog. In addition, the region can be cold in all seasons. So do not forget to take a summer overall and a raincoat with you.</string>
    <string name="savsat_info">Karagöl Sahara National Park, located 45 kilometers north of Artvins Şavşat district, is very famous for its forests, meadows and lake. The national park has two fields, namely Karagöl and Sahara. While there are forests, meadows and lakes in the Karagöl section, plateau tourism comes to the fore in the Sahara section. It is possible to walk in a magnificent nature, get plenty of oxygen and take postcard photographs in the national park, where there are various opportunities and entrance is provided for 25 TL per day.</string>
    <string name="created_date">10/25/2020</string>
</resources>